(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-22T03:00:46.328462",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
The night shines brighter when she sings...
Special guests are here to join the fun, so don't blink
The moment we've all been waiting for...
ルララ ルラ ルララ
Lulala lula lulala
こんなことになるなんて
I never thought things would turn out like this
出会う前に分かってたなら
If I had known before we met,
もう少しだけしゃんとした僕を
I would've shown you a slightly more proper side of me,
見せれたはずなんだ
I'm sure I could have.
どうしたらいいのかなんて
What should I do?
頭では分かってるけど
I know the answer in my head, but...
何気ないちょっとした言葉で
Just a few casual, simple words...
嬉しい顔が出ちゃって
And a joyful expression slips onto my face.
こんなバレバレじゃカッコ悪いな
It's so obvious, it's pretty uncool.
けどこのままじゃ引き下がれないよな
But I can't just back down like this.
でもいざ向かうと照れくさくて
But when I'm right in front of you, I get so shy.
あなたのことが好きだなんて言えないんです
I just can't say that I love you.
この気持ち伝わるかな
I wonder if these feelings will reach you.
浮き足立って空回り
Getting ahead of myself and spinning my wheels,
何も言えずまたサヨナラ
I say goodbye again without saying anything.
あなたのことが好きすぎてたまらないんです
I love you so much, I can't help myself.
明日こそは言えるかな
I wonder if I can say it tomorrow.
あなたも僕と同じように
If you felt the same way as me...
恋してたら…なんて考えちゃうんだ
...and were in love too, I can't help but dream.
会えない日が続いている
The days we can't meet keep going on.
このままじゃよろしくない
This isn't good if it stays like this.
会ったところで何ができるって
It's not like I can do much
わけじゃないんだけど
even if we did meet, though...
こんな恋は二度とないな
A love like this will never happen again.
頭では分かってるけど
I know that in my head, but...
眩しすぎるその笑顔が
Your smile is so dazzling...
僕を焦らせるんだ
...it makes me impatient.
ずっと見ていたくなるような
It makes me want to keep looking at you forever,
目をそらしたくなってしまうような
and also makes me want to avert my eyes.
こんな気持ち分かるのかな
I wonder if you understand this feeling.
あなたが笑ってるならそれでいいんです
As long as you're smiling, that's enough for me.
でも隣は僕がいいなあ
But I really wish I could be the one by your side.
もしかしたら実はずっと
Maybe, in fact, all this time
気づいてるんじゃないかな
you've already noticed.
あなたのことが好きすぎてたまらないんです
I love you so much, I can't help myself.
明日こそは
Tomorrow, for sure...
言いたいな
...I want to say it.
全てをひっくり返すくらいの
Enough to turn everything upside down,
粋なセリフは言えそうにないが
I don't think I can say a witty line like that...
どうしたってこの気持ちは
No matter what, these feelings
抑えられそうにはないんだ
don't seem like they can be suppressed.
あなたと出会ったあの日から
Since the day I met you,
ずっと気持ちは変わらない
my feelings have never changed.
けど
But...
あなたのことが好きだなんて
That I like you...
言えないんです
I just can't say it.
この気持ち伝わるかな
I wonder if these feelings will reach you.
浮き足立って空回り
Getting restless and going in circles,
何も言えずまたサヨナラ
saying nothing, and once again, goodbye.
あなたのことが好きすぎて保存版
Because I like you way too much,
たまらないんです
I just can't bear it.
明日こそは言いたいな
Tomorrow for sure, I want to say it.
あなたも僕と同じように
If you, too, just like me,
恋してたら...なんて考えてる
were in love... is what I'm thinking.
でもわかってる
But I know...
考えすぎってこと
...that I'm thinking too much.
Hou! Hou! U-wa-wa-wa
Kombangwa! Kobo Kanaeru at your service!
Let me be your sun to shine your day!
Hi everyone, kombangwa!
コボ・カナエルです！
I'm Kobo Kanaeru!
コボの3D生誕配信へようこそ！
Welcome to Kobo's 3D birthday stream!
Welcome to Kobo Kanaeru's 3D birthday stream...
...2025! パチパチパチ！
...2025! *claps*
How was Kobo's performance? Dou datta?
How was Kobo's performance? How was it?
またギターで出てきたよね。
I came out with a guitar again, didn't I?
え、ちょっと待って。Let me put the guitar down first.
Wait a second. Let me put the guitar down first.
よしよしよしよし。おいしょ。
Okay, okay. There we go.
Okay. Fuuh. Hai.
Okay. Whew. All right.
Once again, welcome to Kobo's 3D birthday stream 2025!
コボの3D生誕配信へようこそ！
Welcome to Kobo's 3D birthday stream!
This time, I, Kobo, will be hosting an idol-mitai concert...
This time, I, Kobo, will be hosting an idol-like concert...
...and 3D birthday stream for about...
...an hour, with a lot of amazing and awesome guests!
I bet you guys can't wait!
Oh, is Kobo's stage different?
Ah, chat! Nice! Nice eyes, chat! You noticed it? Yeah, you're right!
Look at Kobo's new stage!
わあ、デカイ！
Wow, it's huge!
新しいステージや！
It's a new stage!
There's a big Cilus right here.
チルス、大きなチルス。
Cilus, a big Cilus.
むにゅむにゅ、むにゅむにゅ...
Squishy, squishy...
And so many stars! Stars!
Stars! So many stars!
And then, a big... a big rainbow right here!
Big, very big rainbow!
And so many clouds, because...
...I don't know, I think it's just very aesthetic, yeah.
And the floor! Floor!
床見てや！わあ...
Look at the floor! Wow...
なんかパターン、海みたい。
The pattern looks like the sea.
You know, yeah, like my hair! Ehe.
So... um...
Don't forget to take a lot of screenshots, okay? Especially later, okay? Get a lot of screenshots.
Okay? And then post...
...your comments, your moments, your impressions, your everything...
...with the hashtag #3DKobornDay2025 on your SNS!
そして、コボの3D生誕配信...
And, Kobo's 3D birthday stream...
...SNSにハッシュタグ「#3DKobornDay2025」...
...post it on SNS with the hashtag "#3DKobornDay2025"...
...をつけて...
...and then...
...コメントや思い出、感想などなど投稿してね！
...please post your comments, memories, impressions, and so on!
And...
Right, are you guys ready for the next performance?
Okay, let's go to the next performance!
Hmm... wait, I tried to remember...
For my last position... next position...
あ、オッケー！覚えています！
Ah, okay! I remember!
それでは皆さん、準備いいか？
Alright everyone, are you ready?
Let's go to the next song!
とくべつチュして
Give me a special kiss...
Oh baby, I love you じゃ足りない
Oh baby, "I love you" is not enough.
1番大事がいい
I want to be your number one.
君が作るオリジナルの
Your very own original,
とくべつチュして
Special kiss for me.
眩しくて目が覚めて
Dazzled, I wake up...
愛しく思ってよ
...think of me lovingly.
眠り姫のように
Just like Sleeping Beauty,
優しくくちづけて
kiss me gently.
ロマンめいたこの世界
This world is like a romance,
誘惑がかる君がいる
you are here, under a spell of temptation.
すべてに触れずに
Without touching anything,
二人だけでいよう
let's just be the two of us.
私のこと、独占して
Monopolize me,
君だけのものになってもいい
I don't mind becoming yours alone.
なんでもある日の
On a day where we have everything,
なんでもないキスがいい
a simple kiss is fine.
それで
With that...
Oh baby, I love you じゃ足りない
Oh baby, "I love you" is not enough.
君の特別にして
Make me your special one.
ねえもっと give me a kiss, more 私は
Hey, give me more kisses, more... As for me,
君でいっぱいよ
I am so full of you.
ほどけないリボン結び
A ribbon tied so tightly it won't come undone,
小指キュって縛って
wrap it tightly around our pinkies.
そうよ一生、一生がいいの
Yes, forever and ever is what I want.
特別がほしい
I want something special.
二人きり週末は
During the weekend with just the two of us,
奏でてよハーモニー
play a harmony for me.
流れ星見たら
If we see a shooting star,
私を思って
think of me.
甘々な君なのに
Even though you are normally so sweet,
広い街吸い込まれ
you get swallowed up by the wide city.
他愛ない姿に
At your silly, innocent appearance,
お熱い花丸だね
you get a passionate gold star.
好きなところ 優しいところ
The things I like about you, your gentle side,
嫌いなところも 優しいところ
even your bad side, and your gentle side.
誰にもあげない
I won't give them to anyone,
私だけ独り占め
I'll keep them all to myself!
あぁだって今までの人と
But you see, compared to everyone else before,
同じは嫌いなんです
I don't want us to be the same.
ねえもっと give me more love 私のため
Hey, give me more love, for my sake,
生きてほしいんです
I want you to live for me.
だからうさぎと私は
That's why bunnies and I...
寂しくさせないで
...don't let us get lonely.
それじゃ束縛じゃないわ
But that's not being possessive,
苦しいのが好き
I just love it when it hurts a little.
ショートケーキ 苺みたいに
Like the strawberry on a shortcake,
座っていてもいい？
is it okay if I sit here?
赤く甘い恋だもん
Because this is a red, sweet love,
誰もがうらやむ
everyone is jealous.
大好きも
My love too...
お返ししてもらって全部私に
...return it all back to me.
頂戴、もっと！
Give it to me, even more!
君は神様が作る
You are someone created by God,
奇跡のような人
just like a miracle.
拗ねた顔も その寝顔も
Your sulking face, and your sleeping face too,
守ってあげる、うふふ
I will protect them all, hehe.
Oh baby, I love you じゃ足りない
Oh baby, "I love you" is not enough.
君の特別にして
Make me your special one.
ねえもっと give me a kiss, more 私は
Hey, give me more kisses, more... As for me,
君でいっぱいよ
I am so full of you.
ほどけないリボン結び
A ribbon tied so tightly it won't come undone,
小指キュって縛って
wrap it tightly around our pinkies.
ねえベイビー、最初で最後の
Hey baby, make me your first and last,
特別にしてね
Special one.
うわーーー！
Whoa!
てんてんてん てんてんてん
Ten-ten-ten, ten-ten-ten...
てんてん天国 地獄獄
He-He-Heaven, He-Hell, Hell...
オープンセサミ
Open Sesame!
闇と光の交わるファースト・ピック
First pick where light and darkness intersect,
今宵味わうサイケデリック
tonight we taste the psychedelic.
踊り絡まりあうデリアック
Dancing and tangling up in delirium,
恋の駆け引きのタイム・ブレイク
a time break in the game of love.
うざったい存在
An annoying existence,
ただ気を引きたい
I just want to catch your eye.
夢見心地 触れ合い
Dreamy feelings, touching...
惑わせたい
...I want to confuse you.
曖昧 解けない
Ambiguous, unresolved...
ハローは甘い
Hello is sweet,
鮮やかな赤い愛 見つめて限界
looking at the vivid red love, I'm at my limit.
月夜に誘われて
Invited by the moonlit night,
天使と悪魔と
an angel and a demon,
an angel and a demon...
悪魔が かましかましかました
The demon has shown off, shown off!
天国 地獄の
Heaven and Hell's...
狭間で出会った
We met in the gap between them,
天使と悪魔と
an angel and a demon,
an angel and a demon...
悪魔が 集って踊れば
If the demons gather and dance,
天国 地獄の
Heaven and Hell's...
天国 地獄の 門が開く
Heaven and Hell's gates will open!
闇と光の交わるファナティック
A fanatic clash where light and dark intertwine,
今宵味わうサイケデリック
tasting a psychedelic tonight.
踊り絡まり合うゾディアック
A zodiac dancing and tangling together,
恋の駆け引きの大ブレイク
a big break of romantic strategy!
Dead! Alive!
Death! Death! Death!
Birth! Birth! Birth!
Dead! Alive!
Death! Death! Death! Birth! Birth! Birth!
Let's go!
生けた魂をトレイに置いて
Placing the living soul on a tray,
巡るドミノのカード 揺れる炎
cards of circling dominoes, a flickering flame.
先にあなたがリリースしたら
If you release yours first,
もう迷わない グラス 飲み干して
I'll hesitate no more, draining my glass...
今夜オールイン 終わらないこの勝負保存
Tonight, we're all-in! This match won't end!
今、天国と地獄を繋ぐ門が開いた！
Now, the gates connecting Heaven and Hell have opened!
天使と悪魔、
Angels and demons,
死者と生者が入り乱れ、
the dead and the living mingle,
踊り、笑い、
dancing, laughing...
全ては混沌の中に飲み込まれていく！
Everything is swallowed into the chaos!
それは世界の終焉であり、新たなる始まりでもあるのだった！
It is the end of the world, but also a new beginning!
Dead! Alive!
Death! Death! Death!
Birth! Birth! Birth!
Dead! Alive!
Death! Death! Death! Birth! Birth! Birth!
天 天 天 天国 天
Hea- hea- hea- Heaven, Hea-
天 天 天 天国 地獄
Hea- hea- hea- Heaven, Hell!
天 天 天 天国 天
Hea- hea- hea- Heaven, Hea-
天 天 天 天国 地獄
Hea- hea- hea- Heaven, Hell!
天 天 天 天国 天
Hea- hea- hea- Heaven, Hea-
天 天 天 天国 地獄
Hea- hea- hea- Heaven, Hell!
天 天 天 天国 天
Hea- hea- hea- Heaven, Hea-
天 天 天 天国 地獄
Hea- hea- hea- Heaven, Hell!
月夜に誘われて
Invited by the moonlit night,
天使と悪魔と
an angel and a demon,
an angel and a demon...
悪魔が かましかましかました
The demon has shown off, shown off!
天国 地獄の
Heaven and Hell's...
恍惚 消えない 果てない ムーンライト
ecstasy, never fading, endless moonlight...
天国 地獄の
Heaven and Hell's...
狭間で出会った
We met in the gap between them,
天使と悪魔と
an angel and a demon,
an angel and a demon...
悪魔が 集って踊れば
If the demons gather and dance,
天国 地獄の
Heaven and Hell's...
狭間で出会った
We met in the gap between them,
天使と悪魔と
an angel and a demon,
an angel and a demon...
悪魔が
If the demons
集って踊れば保存
gather and dance,
Dead! Alive!
天 天 天 天国 天
Hea- hea- hea- Heaven, Hea-
天 天 天 天国 地獄
Hea- hea- hea- Heaven, Hell!
Dead! Alive! Dead! Alive!
天 天 天 天国
Hea- hea- hea- Heaven!
天 天 天 天国 地獄
Hea- hea- hea- Heaven, Hell!
天国 地獄！
Heaven! Hell!
Iblis dari mana kah?
What kind of demon are you?
What kind of demon are you?!
Wah, gak tahan orang iblis, wah wah...
Woah, demons are too much to handle, woah woah...
Wahai!
Oh my!
Itu... empat tanduk bahaya sekali.
Those... four horns are extremely dangerous.
Iya, jadi gini...
Yeah, so here's the thing...
Aku datang jauh-jauh...
I came all this way...
Ya, jauh-jauh...
Yeah, all this way...
Apa? Meskipun tidak diundang!
What? Even though I wasn't invited!
Oh, diundang.
Oh, you were invited.
Iya, kayaknya kamu ngundang yang lain deh tadi.
Yeah, I think you invited someone else earlier.
Ma-maksudnya... dou iu imi?
I-I mean... what do you mean?
Kenapa tiba-tiba Nihongo?
Why are you suddenly speaking Japanese?
Kamu malaikat Jepang, ya?
Are you a Japanese angel?
Bisa berhenti muter-muter? Pusing.
Can you stop spinning around? It's making me dizzy.
Pusing, ya? Ya udah.
Dizzy? Alright then.
Malaikat kok pusing, guys. Haduh.
What kind of angel gets dizzy, guys? Seriously.
Iya, aku di sini soalnya datang buat ngerayu kamu aja sebenarnya, pengen main bareng.
Actually, I came here just to charm you, I wanted to play together.
Pengen godain kamu aja.
I just wanted to tease you.
Sini, sini, sini, sini!
Come here, come here!
Pulang, kamu habis ini... loh, kamu habis ini pulang sama aku, kan?保存
Go home with me after this... wait, you're going home with me after this, right?
Pulang?保存
Go home?
Iya, habis ini enggak ada apa-apa lagi, kan?保存
Yeah, there's nothing else after this, right?
Ngapain? Enak-enak aku di atas.
For what? I'm perfectly happy up here.
Masa kamu mau seret aku?
Are you going to drag me?
Loh, kita... loh, bukannya kita...
Wait, we... wait, aren't we...
Kita, kita, kita... Loe aja iblis!
We, we, we... You're the demon here!
Ajak dong, ajak dong, Bang.
Please invite me, please invite me, bro.
Kamu... saya ajak...
You... I invite you...
Aku kesepian.
I'm lonely.
Ayo, sini.
Come on, let's go.
Bareng, ya.
Together, okay?
Fallen angel nih.
A fallen angel here.
Nggak, nggak ada fallen angel. Nggak ada, nggak ada fallen angel ya, guys.
No, there's no fallen angel. There are no fallen angels here, guys.
Bikin aslinya aku panah.
I'll shoot you with my arrow for real.
Iya, iya, coba-coba.保存
Yeah, yeah, give it a try.
Satu, dua, tiga, puh!
One, two, three, puff!
Aakh!
Gila, gila, gila.
Crazy, crazy, crazy.
How to tame your demon.保存
How to tame your demon.
How to tame your...保存
How to tame your...
Jadi light novel.保存
It becomes a light novel.
Gimana tadi freestyle kita? Keren banget ya, guys.
How was our freestyle just now? It was so cool, guys.
Iya, lucu kagak.
Yeah, wasn't it cute?
Atas! Bawah! Atas! Bawah!
Up! Down! Up! Down!
Atas! Bawah! Atas!
Up! Down! Up!
Tapi pas kamu atas, aku bawah.
But when you go up, I go down.
Kebalik.
We're reversed.
Oh iya, orang mah kebalik kiri kanan, dia kebalik atas-atas.
Oh right, people usually swap left and right, but she swaps up and down.
Atas! Atas! Aku bawah. Atas!
Up! Up! I'm down. Up!
Kocak, kocak.
Hilarious, hilarious.
Ya udah kalau gitu, aku... aku wanita sibuk ya sebenarnya.
Alright then, I'm actually a busy woman.
Jadi kayak emang nggak ada... nggak begitu banyak waktu.
So I don't really have that much time.
Idih! Aku di sini mampir, mampir dikit aja bentar.
Gosh! I'm just dropping by, just for a brief moment.
Buset! Kasih-kasih 5 detik buat kamu.
Geez! Let me give you 5 seconds.
Bumi, pemimpin jigoku nih.
A ruler from hell visiting earth.
Asyik! Oke?
Awesome! Okay?
Baik.
Good.
Fiksi ya guys, ini cerita fiksi, jangan ditiru.
This is fiction, guys. This is a fictional story, don't copy it.
Fiksi, fiksi. Sensitif ini, sensitif.
Fiction, fiction. This is sensitive, sensitive.
Fiksi, bohongan. Oke kalau gitu, bye!
Fiction, a lie. Okay then, bye!
Nggak mau ikut aku aja?
Don't you want to come with me?
Nggak mau. Bye bye bye bye!
No way. Bye bye bye bye!
Jagain nih anak ya guys, kita lihat perilakunya beneran seiso atau nggak.
Keep an eye on this kid, guys. Let's see if her behavior is really wholesome or not.
Tuh lihat bajunya, jagain jagain. Ya udah, bye!
Look at her outfit, keep an eye on her! Alright, bye!
Bisa jadi Fallen Angel aku karena hasutan dia, guys.
I could end up becoming a Fallen Angel because of her, guys.
Ngak jelas.
Unbelievable.
どきどきキュンで大暴走
Running wild with a heart-pounding squeeze!
なんとかしなくちゃならなくて 突然メイドになっちゃって
I had to do something about it, and suddenly I became a maid!
いつものようにお店のお掃除 扉開いちゃって目が合った
Cleaning the shop like usual, the door opened and our eyes met!
なんだかソワソワしちゃって おわてんぼうにもなっちゃって
Somehow I got so fidgety and ended up being a scatterbrain!
お仕事中におきに夢中 どこを探しても見当たらないじゃん
In the middle of work, I'm crazy about my favorite, but I can't find them anywhere!
もう一回
One more time!
ちょっと待って
Wait a minute!
もういいよ
It's fine now!
秘密だよね
It's a secret, right?
もういいの？
Is it enough?
好きになっちゃって
I've fallen in love!
ねえ 好きって言って
Hey, say you love me!
どきどきキュン送るラブビーム キミを夢中にさせる魔法じゃん
Sending a heart-pounding love beam, it's magic that makes you crazy about me!
ほらどきどきキュン私大暴走 キミを夢中にさせる恋の味
Look, my heart is pounding and I'm running wild! The taste of love that makes you crazy!
もうキミにキュン私大暴走 キミと夢中になれる魔法じゃん
My heart's squeezing for you, running wild! It's magic that makes us crazy together!
だからキミがキュンてなる恋になって ひとつどうぞこれが恋の味
So fall in love and let your heart squeeze, here you go, this is the taste of love!
楽しくて仕方なくなっちゃって そろそろ終わりになっちゃって
I couldn't help but have so much fun, but now it's almost time to end!
会いたくなって落ち込んじゃって キミとぶつかって目が合った
I wanted to see you and got depressed, but then I bumped into you and our eyes met!
何度も会いたくなっちゃって 今日だけじゃ足りないんだって
I wanted to see you over and over, today alone is just not enough!
計画通り私の勝利 キミに会いたくて仕方がないよ
Just as planned, it's my victory! I can't help but want to see you!
もう一回
One more time!
ちょっと待って
Wait a minute!
もういいの？
Is it enough?
キミだけだよ
It's only you!
もうずっと
Forever and ever,
愛し合いたいよね
I want us to love each other!
ねえ 好きって言って
Hey, say you love me!
どきどきキュンキミにラブビーム 二人夢中になれる魔法じゃん
Heart-pounding squeeze, a love beam to you! It's magic that makes us both crazy!
ほらどきどきキュン私大恋愛 キミも夢中にさせる恋のマキ
Look, my heart is pounding in great romance! The volume of love making you crazy too!
もうキミにキュン私大興奮 キミと夢中になれる魔法じゃん
My heart's squeezing for you, I'm super excited! It's magic that makes us crazy together!
だからキミはキュンてなる恋に落ちて ひとつどうぞこれが恋の味
So fall in love and let your heart squeeze, here you go, this is the taste of love!
あーあ このままだったら ここで会うこともなくなって
Ah, if things stay like this, we won't even meet here anymore...
あー キミの声が 聞きたくなるの
Ah, I will start to miss hearing your voice!
もう一回
One more time!
ちょっと待って
Wait a minute!
もういいの？
Is it enough?
秘密なのに
Even though it's a secret!
もういいよ
It's fine now!
このまま好きになってく
I'm falling for you just like this!
好きって言って
Say you love me!
どきどきキュン送るラブビーム キミを夢中にさせる魔法じゃん
Sending a heart-pounding love beam, it's magic that makes you crazy about me!
ほらどきどきキュン私大暴走 キミを夢中にさせる恋の味
Look, my heart is pounding and I'm running wild! The taste of love that makes you crazy!
もうキミにキュン私大暴走 キミと夢中になれる魔法じゃん
My heart's squeezing for you, running wild! It's magic that makes us crazy together!
だからキミがキュンてなる恋になって ひとつどうぞこれが恋の味
So fall in love and let your heart squeeze, here you go, this is the taste of love!
Halo semuanya!
Hello, everyone!
Hehe, langit sudah mulai gelap, tapi...
Hehe, the sky is starting to get dark, but...
masih pada semangat nggak semuanya?!
are you all still hyped?!
たくさんゲストとパフォーマンスしてから、
After performing with so many guests...
次はコボはまた一人で歌いたいなと思います。
Next, Kobo wants to perform solo again!
これから歌うこの曲は、最近コボが気に入っている曲で、
The next song I'm going to sing is a personal favorite lately.
聞いたら幸せな気持ちになりました。
Listening to it filled me with such a happy feeling.
皆さんもこの曲聞いて、幸せを感じてくれたら嬉しいです。
I hope that you can also feel happy when you hear it.
それでは、次の曲、青山テルマさんの「Happiness」です。
Now then, here is my next song: "Happiness" by Thelma Aoyama.
君とHappiness 君がいれば
Happiness with you, as long as you're here
大丈夫だって思えるよ
I feel like everything will be alright
何も言わなくても
Even if we don't say a word
感じてるよ the one for me
I feel it, you're the one for me
Oh, oh, oh, oh
You always make me happy
落ち込んで 眠れなくて
When I'm feeling down and can't sleep
君との写真見つめている
I gaze at our photos together
いくつもの 笑顔たちに
Saved by all the smiles
助けられるよ my life
I'm getting through my life
ずっと一緒だよ 泣いてもいいよ
"We're always together, it's okay to cry"
あの涙を 抱きしめてくれた
You held those tears close to your heart
どこにいるの？ ここにいるから
"Where are you?" "I'm right here"
すぐに会いたいって
Saying we must meet right away
君とHappiness 君がいれば
Happiness with you, as long as you're here
大丈夫だって思えるよ
I feel like everything will be alright
何も言わなくても
Even if we don't say a word
感じてるよ the one for me
I feel it, you're the one for me
君とHappiness どんなときも
Happiness with you, no matter when
一人じゃないって信じてるよ
I believe that I am not alone
涙あふれたって
Even if tears overflow
歩けるよね please stay by my side
We can keep walking, please stay by my side
君に出会えてからは
Ever since I met you
素真に笑っていられるよ(素直に笑っていられるよ)
I can smile genuinely
少しずつ 自分のこと(少しずつ自分のこと)
Step by step, I feel like
好きになれたような
I've come to like myself more
そう今なら ねえ心から
Yes, now, from the bottom of my heart
分かり合えるって思えるよ
I feel like we can understand each other
強がらずに ありのままでを
Without acting tough, you accepted me
見つめてくれた
Just as I am
だからHappiness 君のことを
So Happiness, I want to know
今よりもっと知りたくて
So much more about you than now
どんな言葉よりも
More than any words
大切だよ the one for me
You are precious, the one for me
私も君に何か
I also want to do something
出来ることしたいよ
That I can do for you
いつでも一緒だから
Because we are always together
守っているから
I will protect you
ずっと
Forever...
君とHappiness 君がいれば
Happiness with you, as long as you're here
大丈夫だって思えるよ
I feel like everything will be alright
何も言わなくても
Even if we don't say a word
感じてるよ the one for me
I feel it, you're the one for me
君とHappiness どんなときも
Happiness with you, no matter when
一人じゃないって信じてるよ
I believe that I am not alone
涙あふれたって
Even if tears overflow
歩けるよね please stay by my side
We can keep walking, please stay by my side
大切だよ the one for me
You are precious, the one for me
Let's go!
Oh, oh, oh, oh
You always make me happy
Smile for me baby
Oh, oh, oh, oh
You always make me happy
Smile for me baby
Oh, oh, oh, oh
You always make me happy
ようこそお越しなさったご主人様
Welcome, my master who has come to visit.
隣に座って せーの
Sit down next to me, ready, set...
萌え 萌え 萌え 萌え
Moe moe moe moe!
こんなんで誰が喜ぶのさ
Who would even be happy with this?
ねぇ教えて 笑顔で アップップ
Hey, tell me, with a smile, puff up your cheeks!
愛想は忘れて ご苦労様
Forget the pleasantries, thank you for your hard work.
私とあなたで せーの
You and me, ready, set...
love love love love
こんなんで誰が喜ぶのさ
Who would even be happy with this?
ねぇ教えて 笑顔で アップップ
Hey, tell me, with a smile, puff up your cheeks!
ひらり はらり 女の子
Fluttering, falling, a girl.
ふわり ふわり 言葉のソウ
Softly, softly, a layer of words.
それってつまり お冷めな嬢
Which means, in short, a cold young lady.
感情的リアル 笑顔で アップップ
An emotional reality, with a smile, puff up your cheeks!
人は見かけによらぬもの
People are not what they seem.
嘘を嘘だと見抜けない
You can't see through a lie.
したたかな袖振る革
Shaking sleeves of cunning leather.
鳥肌 寒肌 アンドゥトロワ
Goosebumps, cold skin, un, deux, trois.
間違ったご指名をいただきます
I'll accept your mistaken nomination.
私とあなたで せーの
You and me, ready, set...
love love love love
これはど派手にご苦労様
This is extremely flashy, thank you for your hard work.
遊びましょう 笑顔で アップップ
Let's play, with a smile, puff up your cheeks!
ひらり はらり ここは何処
Fluttering, falling, where is this?
ふわり ふわり 掃討 show
Softly, softly, cleanup show.
それってつまり お冷めな嬢
Which means, in short, a cold young lady.
確証的リアル 笑顔で アップップ
A corroborative reality, with a smile, puff up your cheeks!
歌いだす秘密の鐘
The secret bell begins to sing.
終わることの無いこの世界
In this world that never ends.
悲しい子供は
The sad children...
虚しい子供は
...the empty children...
眠らせて
...let them fall asleep.
おままごと 遊びましょう
Let's play house...
笑顔で アップップ
...with a smile, puff up your cheeks!
ひらり はらり 女の子
Fluttering, falling, a girl.
ふわり ふわり 言葉のソウ
Softly, softly, a layer of words.
それってつまり お冷めな嬢
Which means, in short, a cold young lady.
感情的リアル 笑顔で アップップ
An emotional reality, with a smile, puff up your cheeks!
遊びましょう 笑顔で アップップ
Let's play, with a smile, puff up your cheeks!
アップップ
Puff up your cheeks!
Let's dance with me!
何回でもかける true magic
Casting true magic over and over again.
まだまだ今日は夢見心地
We're still in a dreamlike state today.
眠たくても簡単再現
Even if we're sleepy, it's easily recreated.
何度もおかえりって once again
Saying 'welcome back' over and over, once again.
朝が来るその時まで
Until the morning comes...
ねぇ 僕とどうだい
...hey, how about with me?
塞ぎ込んでる 週の終わりに
At the end of a gloomy week,
退屈そうだけどどうだろう
you look bored, but what do you think?
誘っていいかな
Can I invite you?
Come on, night! Come on, ride! かも分かんない
Come on, night! Come on, ride! I don't even know.
どっち向いてる？ こっち向いてる？
Which way are you looking? This way?
あっち向いてワン！ なんかじゃなくて
Not like 'look over there, woof!'
キミのことだもん
Since it's about you,
もっとちゃんと話聞いてよ
listen to me more properly!
劣勢から逆転？
A turnaround from a disadvantage?
昨日より今日の方がカワイイし<
You're cuter today than yesterday,
いてもたってもいられない
and I just can't sit still!
聞こえる 0時告げるチャイム
I hear the chime announcing midnight,
時間切れの先へ
heading beyond the time limit.
飛び出して 駆け出して
Jump out, run out,
まだまだ夜終われない
the night still can't end!
こんなサイコーな日々が
If days this amazing
明日も続いてくなら
will continue tomorrow as well...
ねぇ キミもどうだい
...hey, how about you too?
待ち望んでる キミの理想の
For the ideal princess seat
お姫様の席をどうしよう
you've been waiting for, what should we do?
狙っていいかな
Can I aim for it?
Make a chance, let's dance! え、今じゃない！？
Make a chance, let's dance! Eh, not right now?!
猫も杓子も曲に合わせて
Everyone and their dog matches the song,
ステップなんか踏んでみて ご機嫌そう
stepping around, looking so happy.
昨日より今日がずっと楽しくて
Today is much more fun than yesterday,
続けたいときには
and when we want to keep going...
聞こえる 0時告げるチャイム
I hear the chime announcing midnight,
時間切れの先へ
heading beyond the time limit.
終わらない 止まらない
It won't end, it won't stop,
まだまだ夜長いから
because the night is still long!
こんなサイコーなリズムに
To a rhythm this amazing...
リズムに
To the rhythm,
体を預けてみたら
if you surrender your body,
ほら 魔法みたい
look, it's like magic.
いつものグルーヴ口ずさもう 騒がしくて馬鹿らしいような フライ 毎日がいい
Let's hum our usual groove, a noisy, silly, flying everyday is great!
魔法なんてあり得ない でも今夜だけは現実になるかも
Magic is impossible, but maybe just for tonight it will become real.
体揺らして 音に登って
Sway your body, climb onto the sound...
踊れ 君も
and dance, you too.
終わらない夜に とびきりの魔法
On this endless night, a special magic...
君にもかけてあげるから
I'll cast it on you too.
僕の手をとってよ
So take my hand.
聞こえる鳴り止まないミュージック 魔法が解けるまで
You can hear the non-stop music, until the magic is broken,
最高で最強な夜が今日も更けていく
this wonderful, strongest night is deepening again today.
こんな夢みたいな日々が明日も続いていくなら
If days like a dream like this continue tomorrow too...
ねえ
Hey,
君はどうしたい？アンコール 大胆に夜を飾るソング
what do you want to do? An encore song boldly decorating the night,
何回でもかける呪文 まだまだ続く夢心地
a spell cast over and over. This dreamlike state will go on.
嘘みたいだけど 朝が来るその時まで
It feels like a lie, but until the morning comes,
ねえ 僕と踊らない？
hey, won't you dance with me?
うわあ！きゃあ！
Waaah! Kyaaa!
ここはどこ？
Where are we?
分かんない！
I don't know!
え？なんか雲美味しそうじゃない？
Eh? Doesn't that cloud look delicious?
食べてみなよ。
Go ahead and try eating it.
あーん！
Ahhh!
おお、美味しい。
Oh, it's delicious.
美味しい！
It's delicious!
ゼタ、食べて。にゃ。
Zeta, eat some. Nya.
何をしてるの！
What are you doing!
ああ！コボ！
Ah! Kobo!
ああ！初めは食べてないです！
Ah! We didn't eat it at first!
見守ってた、見守ってた！
We were just watching, just watching!
初めは食べてないです！
We didn't eat it at first!
私の雲！
My cloud!
こら！誰が･･･
Hey! Who did...
Tanya Zeta!
Ask Zeta!
Tanya Anya!
Ask Anya!
Tanya Anya, tanya Zeta!
Ask Anya, ask Zeta!
Zeta yang makan! / Anya yang makan!
Zeta ate it! / Anya ate it!
Zeta yang makan!
Zeta ate it!
何をしてるの？
What are you doing?
But Kobo, today is your birthday!
誕生日！Happy Birthday!
Your birthday! Happy Birthday!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
Happy birthday, Kobo!
へえ、じゃあ･･･
Hehe, well then...
コボ先輩と一緒に歌って踊りたい！
I want to sing and dance with Kobo-senpai!
歌って踊りたい！
Want to sing and dance!
オッケー、オッケー。
Okay, okay.
コボの振り付け。
Kobo's choreography.
Very nice!
コボの･･･コボ先生と呼んでください。
Kobo's... Please call me Kobo-sensei.
コボちゃん！
Kobo-chan!
ガキだとう！
Calling me a kid?!
じゃ、勉強した？
So, did you study?
もちろん！
Of course!
I study Kobo-senpai's choreograph...
I studied Kobo-senpai's choreograph...
Choreography.
Choreography, な。じゃ、行きますよ。
Choreography, right. Let's go then.
行きましょう、オッケー！
Let's go, okay!
おお、いいね。ポジショニングオッケー！
Oh, nice. Positioning OK!
オッケー！
OK!
ポジショニングオッケー！オッケー、じゃ、行きましょう。
Positioning OK! OK, well, let's go.
誰も居なくなった
Everyone has disappeared
二人だけの街に
into this town of only the two of us,
機械仕掛けの時計が
where the clockwork clock
夜の訪れ知らせる
announces the arrival of the night.
夕闇が空を
The evening twilight
ワイン色に染めて
dyes the sky a wine red,
不慣れな二人を
and invites our clumsy selves
舞台へと誘う
onto the stage.
Chasse 'n' Whisk 'n' Natural-Turn
貴方に魔法をあげる
I will cast a magic spell on you.
Throwaway and Oversway
その名前は honey mead
Its name is honey mead.
蜜月 Un・Deux・Trois
Honeymoon Un Deux Trois.
互いの指を絡めて
Intertwining our fingers together.
Sing, swing, swing, sweetest song
二人の夢を奏でる
Playing out our two dreams
Chase and whisk and natural tour
あなたに魔法をかける
I will cast a spell on you
Throw away and over sway
魅惑の蜜 ハニーハニー
Enticing nectar, honey, honey
Un, deux, trois
One, two, three
どの唇を重ねて
Whose lips should overlap?
Sing, swing, swing, sweetest song
二人の愛を奏でる
Playing out our love
月明かりが彼女の
The moonlight shines upon her
黄金色に照らして
lighting her up in golden hues
幼い二人は
The innocent pair...
つまずきながら踊る
dances while stumbling along
Un, deux, trois
One, two, three
互いの指を絡めて
intertwining each other's fingers
Sing, swing, swing, sweetest song
二人の夢を奏でる
We play out our two dreams
シャバダバ Un, deux, trois
Shabadaba, One, two, three
その唇を重ねて
Overlapping those lips
Sing, swing, swing, sweetest song
二人の愛を奏でる
Playing out our love
楽しかった！ / 楽しかったね！
That was so fun! / It really was!
やったー！
We did it!
おー、ダンス上手、ダンス上手！
Oh, you guys are so good at dancing!
ありがとう、ありがとう / Makasih!
Thank you, thank you! / Thank you!
なんか、スワン？ / Kobo先輩もスワン
Like... a swan? / Kobo-senpai is a swan too.
スワン、奏もスワン / Beautiful swan!
A swan, Kanade is a swan too. / Beautiful swan!
スワンスワン！
Swan, swan!
優雅、優雅！ / めっちゃエレガント！
Graceful, graceful! / So elegant!
エレガント！ / お疲れ様！
Elegant! / Great work!
これ踊るの難しかった？
Was this dance difficult?
ええ、ちょっと... / 嘘！
Well, a little... / No way!
大丈夫、簡単です、簡単だよ！
It's fine, it's easy, so easy!
楽しかった！ / 来てくれてありがとうね
That was fun! / Thank you for coming.
Kobo先輩、呼んでくれてありがとう
Kobo-senpai, thank you for inviting us!
ありがとう！ / Makasih, makasih!
Thank you! / Thank you, thank you!
一緒に踊ってくれてもありがとう
And thank you for dancing with me.
Sama-sama! / Sama-sama!
You're welcome! / You're welcome!
Sama-sama! Sama-sama!
You're welcome! You're welcome!
Happy Birthday! / おめでとう！
Happy Birthday! / Congratulations!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
じゃ、バイバイ！ / バイバイ！
Well, bye-bye! / Bye-bye!
みんな帰っちゃった...
Everyone went home...
寂しい...
I'm lonely...
悲しい... 誰も来ないのかな...
So sad... I wonder if no one else is coming...
でも、
But...
さよならの前にキスをして
Kiss me before we say goodbye
さよならの後は忘れさせて
Make me forget after the goodbye
でもあなたの名前が消えない
But your name won't fade
離れない
I can't let go
話せない
I can't let you go
戻りたい
I want to go back
Take me free
Set me free
この夜が君を奪いたがる
This night wants to steal you away
とどまった色味
The lingering colors...
部屋の中は香水だらけに染めた Jasmine flavor
I dyed the room with perfume, a scent of jasmine flavor.
当たり前さえも奇跡 当たり障れない君との軌跡
Even the mundane is a miracle, this path with you where we never clashed.
どれだけ恋い慕っても 超えられない君を
No matter how deeply I yearn for you, I can never reach you.
今なら分かる気がして
I feel like I understand now.
今から過去に戻れるなら
If only I could go back to the past now...
サヨナラの前に キスをして
Give me a kiss before we say goodbye.
サヨナラの後は 忘れさせて
Make me forget after we say goodbye.
でもあなたの名前が消えない
But your name won't fade away.
離れない 離せない 戻りたい
I can't leave, I can't let go, I want to go back.
Take me free
呪いたいほど愛しているのよ
I love you so much it feels like a curse.
気づけばあなたのことばかり浮かべて
Before I know it, only thoughts of you fill my mind.
明日になれば 大丈夫
Once tomorrow comes, I'll be fine.
何度言い聞かせればいいの
How many times do I have to tell myself that?
愛という沼に 溺れている
I'm drowning in a swamp called love.
私の声は 届かない
My voice doesn't reach you.
サヨナラの前に キスをして
Give me a kiss before we say goodbye.
サヨナラの後は 忘れさせて
Make me forget after we say goodbye.
Demo anata no namae ga kienai
But your name won't fade away.
離れない 離せない 戻りたい
I can't leave, I can't let go, I want to go back.
Take me free
サヨナラの前に キスをして
Give me a kiss before we say goodbye.
サヨナラの後は 忘れさせて
Make me forget after we say goodbye.
でもあなたの名前が消えない
But your name won't fade away.
離れない
I can't leave you.
離さない
I won't let go.
戻れない
I can't go back.
Take me free
絶え間ない日々
These endless days...
抱きしめたまま
...as I hold them close.
いつか そう いつか
Someday... yes, someday...
弱い心が 捕まる前に
...before my weak heart gets captured...
そっと あなたを遠ざけた
...I gently pushed you away.
あぁ こんな気持ち
Ah, this kind of feeling...
辛すぎるよ もう
...is just too painful already.
あなたは 誰なの
Who are you?
どこに 隠れてたの
Where have you been hiding?
ひどく 怯えてる
Terribly frightened...
うつむいたままの
...with my head cast down.
見慣れない 私が
An unfamiliar version of myself...
泣いてた
...was crying.
またあの季節
That season has come again.
夜空は白く
The night sky turns white...
あなたもいて
...and you are there.
触れてこないで
Please don't reach out and touch me.
嬉しいけれど
Even though it makes me happy...
心が痛い
...my heart aches.
離したくない
I don't want to let go.
離れたくない
I don't want to be apart.
でも諦めてた
But I had already given up.
もうこれ以上
Any more than this...
好きになれない
...I cannot love you.
失う痛み
The pain of losing you...
耐え切れないよ
...is more than I can bear.
絶え間ない日々
These endless days...
抱きしめたまま
...as I hold them close.
いつか そう いつか
Someday... yes, someday...
ただ側にいて
Just stay by my side.
それだけでいい
That's all I need.
素直にはなれないけれど
Although I can't be honest with you.
さあ 顔を上げて
Come, lift up your head
歩み始めなきゃ
And start walking forward
リアルな私を 愛してよ
Please love the real me...
気付いて
...and notice me
またあの季節 この空の下
Once again, under this sky in that season...
見上げている
...I am looking up
傷ついたもの もう元には 戻らないけど
What's been broken can never go back to how it was, but...
そう...
Still...
離したくない 離れたくない
I don't want to let go, I don't want to be apart
もう諦めない
I won't give up anymore
あなたの心 傷つけてでも
Even if it hurts your heart...
この気持ちに 嘘はつけない
...I cannot lie to these feelings
いつか笑顔で 話せるような
So that one day we can talk with a smile...
私を見つけて
...please find me
嵐の日にいて 聞かせてほしい
Stay with me on stormy days, I want to hear you say...
二度と一人にはしないと
...that you'll never leave me alone again
変わり映えない日々 抱きしめたまま
While holding onto these unchanging days...
きっと そう きっと
...surely, yes, surely...
あの日の気持ち 受け止めないと
...if I don't accept my feelings from that day,
前に進むことができない
I won't be able to move forward
離したくない 離れたくない
I don't want to let go, I don't want to be apart
一つの願いは
My one and only wish...
大好きだよと 伝えたいだけ
...is just to tell you that I love you
本当 素直じゃないけれど
Even though I'm really not honest with myself
So...
How is it, guys?
How was it, guys?
The last closing...
The last closing song...
Did you take a lot of screenshots? Ooh.
Did you take a lot of screenshots?
And, ah, how about my new stage?
And, how about my new stage?
Look! Whoa!
It's very cloudy here.
Yeah, as you can see, there's two big Gilles on the left and right.
Yeah, as you can see, there are two big Gilles on the left and right.
めちゃ綺麗！
It's so beautiful!
みんなどうだった？ このパフォーマンス
How was it, everyone? This performance...
いっぱいスクリーンショット撮れたかな？
Did you take lots of screenshots?
この新しいステージは、どうだった？
How did you like this new stage?
可愛いでしょ！
It's cute, right?!
ビッグGillesが、ありますのでめちゃ可愛いよね！
Since there are big Gilles here, it's super cute, right?!
So, actually...
Yeah, we are already at the end of the show, guys, but...
そろそろ、お別れの時間になりますよ。
It is almost time to say goodbye.
But don't worry.
Kobo still has something to share with you guys.
まだ皆さんに、お知らせがあります！
I still have an announcement for you all!
じゃ、じゃじゃーん！
Ta-da!
Kobo Kanaeru Special Birthday 2025 Merch Set!
This time Kobo's Birthday Merch Set is Jellyfish...
This time, Kobo's Birthday Merch Set is Jellyfish-themed...
Princess!
I've wanted to wear a jellyfish costume for a long time.
And finally, my wish came true!
So, how is it, guys?
Do I look beautiful?
And the KV is drawn by Scuooty-sensei.
And the key visual is drawn by Scuooty-sensei.
Scuooty-sensei, thank you!
Thank you!
And as you wish, guys...
Finally, tada!
Kobokers' Happi is here!
Now you guys can be proud Kobokers,
and perfect for cheering me during events!
Keren banget.
It's so cool.
Happi, Happi, Happi!
Come on, buy Happi, Happi. And if you look closely,
this Happi design is like...
is like my raincoat, right?
And you can see there's Chillus
in the front, and me
in the back, right?
And...
Next!
We have this...
"Jellyfish Princess on the Wall" Tapestry!
It's printed with my brand new birthday illustration.
It's super high quality and perfect
for decorating your wall.
You can wake up
and see Kobo's smug face every morning,
and also don't forget to praise the Lord every day!
Then, look at this!
The "Jellyfish Princess, you got this"
Button Badge Set!
Two pieces!
One has my birthday outfit,
and the other is an illustration I drew by myself.
Yeah, by myself.
It looks good, right?
Do you like it? I drew it by myself.
So you can pin them to your bag,
or your head,
or your heart!
Okay, so this one...
is one of my favorites!
One, two, three...
Tada! The plush keychain!
Tada! The plushie keychain!
It's me!
But mini Kobo, in mini form!
You can bring me anywhere!
On your backpack, your keys,
your motorcycle,
the car, whatever,
even next to your computer while you watch my streams!
So soft and squishy!
And finally,
we also have the Situational Voice Pack!
So it's called...
"Your One and Only Jellyfish Princess".
What does it mean?!
Buy it!
Buy it, okay? So you know what does it mean!
Yippee! It's a special voice pack
where I talk to you about Jellyfish Princess,
and, you know, your one and only just for you!
Yeah, don't miss out on my birthday merch, guys!
If you buy the set also,
you'll get a special bromide with my signature on it.
you'll get a special bromide card with my signature on it.
The merch is available for a limited time only,
so you can grab yours...
from the official shop,
links are in the description!
So yeah, that's all for the announcement.
Thank you for coming and watching
Kobo's performance today.
以上グッズのお知らせでした。
That's all for the merchandise announcement.
説明欄やチャット欄にリンクを貼ってありますので
The links are in the description and chat section,
クリックしてね！
so click them!
Oh, yeah! But...
I can hear some of you want an encore?
Encore? Encore? アンコール欲しい？
Encore? Encore? Do you want an encore?
じゃ、しょうがないわ。
Well, I guess I have no choice.
Please listen, "Sweet Memories".
なつかしい
A familiar...
痛みだわ
...ache.
ずっと前に
I had completely...
忘れていた
...forgotten.
でもあなたを見たとき
But when I saw you,
時間だけ後戻りしたの
time turned backward for a moment.
「幸福？」と
Don't ask me...
聞かないで
...if I'm happy.
嘘つくのは上手じゃない
I'm not very good at lying.
友達なら
I have...
いるけれど
...friends,
あんなには燃えあがれなくて
but I can't burn as brightly as I did then.
失った
Why is it only...
夢だけが
...the lost dreams...
美しく見えるのはなぜかしら
...that seem so beautiful?
過ぎ去った
Even your long-past...
優しさも
...kindness...
今は
...is now...
甘い記憶 SWEET MEMORIES
...a sweet memory, sweet memories.
Don't kiss me baby we can never be
So don't add more pain
Please don't hurt me again
I have spent so many nights
Thinking of you longing for your touch
I have once loved you so much
I once loved you so much.
あの頃は
Back then...
若すぎて
...we were much too young...
悪戯に傷つけあった二人
...and we hurt each other for no reason.
色褪せた
Even our faded...
哀しみも
...sadness...
今は
...is now...
遠い記憶 SWEET MEMORIES
...a distant memory, sweet memories.
失った
Why is it only...
夢だけが
...the lost dreams...
美しく見えるのはなぜかしら
...that seem so beautiful?
過ぎ去った
Even your long-past...
優しさも
...kindness...
今は
...is now...
甘い記憶 SWEET MEMORIES
...a sweet memory, sweet memories.
君はほんとにわかってないよ
You really don't understand.
例えば ハッピー
For example, rather than a happy...
エンドより 甘くて豪華な デザートより
...ending, or a sweet, gorgeous dessert,
君がいいんだよ
I want you.
ふたつの傘より 相合い傘
Sharing an umbrella rather than having two,
ちょっと冷たいけど
it's a bit cold, though...
愛するための代償ならいくらでもどうぞ
But if it's the price for loving, take whatever you want.
ただずっと側にいたい
I just want to be by your side forever.
ねえ ダーリン 星屑もない
Hey, darling, there isn't even any stardust...
ふたりぼっちの 世界でずっと
...in this world of just the two of us forever.
最後の花火をあげて フィナーレを飾って
Let's set off the last firework and decorate the finale.
奇跡の降る 恋に落ちて
Falling in love where miracles rain down,
ダーリン もう離さないで
darling, don't ever let me go.
味気ない世界も悪くないね
This bland world isn't so bad, is it?
どんなに恋をしたって 出逢えないよきっと
No matter how many times I fall in love, I'll never meet someone like you.
終わりのない幸せにキスをしよう
Let's kiss for endless happiness.
いつか今日を 忘れても
Even if we forget today one day,
君がいいんだよ
I still want you.
天気雨の日 言い合いっこして
On the day of the sun shower, we argued,
はじめて目が合った ずっと覚えておくよ
and our eyes met for the first time... I'll remember it forever.
ねえ ダーリン 星屑もない
Hey, darling, there isn't even any stardust...
ふたりぼっちの 世界でずっと
...in this world of just the two of us forever.
最後の花火をあげて フィナーレを誓って
Let's set off the last firework and vow to the finale.
奇跡の降る 恋に落ちて
Falling in love where miracles rain down,
ダーリン もう離さないで
darling, don't ever let me go.
そっ気ない世界も悪くないね
This cold world isn't so bad, is it?
どんなに恋をしたって 忘れられないの
No matter how many times I fall in love, I can never forget.
終わりのない幸せにキスをしよう
Let's kiss for endless happiness.
味気ないね
It's bland, isn't it?
でもそれがね
But you see, that...
ふたりの幸せ
...is our happiness.
Oh my god, I almost cried. I almost cried singing this song.
Thank you for today, guys. Thank you for today. Thank you for watching until the end.
And thank you for Zeta-nee, because she covered this finale song first and then I was inspired.
So yeah, Kobo baru... hehehe
So yeah, Kobo just... hehehe.
今日は来てくれて、今日は来てくれて、最後まで見てくれてありがとうございました！
Thank you for coming today, and thank you for watching until the end!
I hope you guys enjoy all the performances...
...this whole stream!
みんな大好き！ Thank you for your birthday wishes! 後で読んであげますね、うん。
I love you all! Thank you for your birthday wishes! I'll read them later.
Bye-bye, minna! No more encore, no more encore. Bye-bye!
Bye-bye, everyone! No more encore, no more encore. Bye-bye!
Bokobokobo! Kobo Kanaeru at your service, let me be your sun to shine your day!
Bye-byee!
んー、まっ！
Mwah!
Thank you!
I can't be as bright as now Without you!
-Kobo